Name: Craig Taylor

<u>Address:</u> 80 Edward Tyler Road, London, SE12 9QF

Mobile: 07908 795936

Email: craigtaylor89@yahoo.co.uk

Github: https://github.com/BrightReach

## Profile

Junior Programmer with experience using C++/C#, HTML, CSS, SASS, Javascript, React.js, Node.js, Express.js, Wordpress, MySQL, PHP and Git. A friendly and passionate individual who is willing to take on new challenges while striving and determined to be the best he can be.

## **Personal Projects**

Udacity Capstone Project | Github Link | Javascript, Node.js, Express.js, Jest, Webpack

As part of the final project of the Udacity nanodegree, I was tasked with creating a search engine based on where the user intends to travel. With the current implementation, this would enable the user to search for the destination based on the keyword used, set the date of when the user will arrive and optionally return and retrieve a picture and the weather forecast of the said destination.

Dungeon Escape | Github Link | Unity3D, C#

Dungeon Escape is part of a Unity approved course that will further train my knowledge in C# as well as utilise the intermediate functionality of the game engine. Once I have completed the coursework in full, this will become an ongoing project where I will implement further mechanics and enemy varieties as a resemblance of the Metroidvania genre.

## Work Experience

## Homestead LCI Ltd - Barista

November 2020 to Present

Homestead is a small and independent business based on the London City Island in Canning Town. It not only acts as a restaurant and cafe, but it also acts as a retail, fishmonger, butcher, florist and grocer under the same roof. The main principle is to provide products that are high in quality but is also sustainable, ethical and local.

#### TT Fusion Ltd – QA Tester

July to November 2015

LEGO Marvel's Avengers -PS3/PS4/Xbox 360/Xbox One/Wii U

TT Fusion Ltd. (formerly Embryonic Studios Ltd.) is a British video game developerment and a division of TT Games. Based in Wilmslow, England, United Kingdom

- Conducted Smoke Testing to ensure the player is able to naturally progress from the start of the game without any progression blockers that would ruin the experience.
- Conducted Scripted/Regression/Sweep testing based on Lead QA's instructions and Destructive testing to identify unreported bugs and ensure fixes are in place from Regression testing.

 Observed, analysed and reported evidential bugs using JIRA based on its severity and urgency with Lead QA's approval to ensure upmost quality, challenge and enjoyment upon release.

# SEGA Europe Ltd - Functionality Tester

October 2014 to July 2015

SEGA, is a Japanese multinational video game developer and publisher headquartered in Tokyo, Japan, with multiple offices around the world. Sega developed and manufactured numerous home video game consoles from 1983 to 2001.

Games worked on: Total War: ARENA, Dead Island 2

# Qualifications

Udacity Front-end Developer

BA (Hons) Game Design – Tiga Accredited - First Class Honours

BTEC National Diploma for Games Development (DDD)

BTEC First Diploma in IT - Merit

BTEC Introductory Diploma for IT at Work – Distinction

City & Guilds Key Skills Communication Level 2 – Pass

City & Guilds Key Skills Application on Numbers Level 2 – Pass

### Hobbies

Console, PC & Mobile Gaming
Martial Arts
Music Composition & Singing
Cooking & Speciality Coffee Brewing

References

Available upon request.